cloudwifi.com 2016-02-05

# Mojo Networks - Leaders In Scalable Secure Cloud Managed WiFi Privacy Policy

Mojo Networks respects your privacy and understands your need to protect the personal information that you share with us. This policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

## Information Collected

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, or birth date. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us your personal information. We don't automatically collect personal information, including your email address. We do collect your Internet related information, such as, your Internet Protocol (IP) address (the Internet address of your computer), the domain you use to access the Internet, the web site you came from and the web site you visit next. If you have previously given us your personal information, then we may link your IP address to that information and therefore, when you browse our website, you may not be anonymous. In addition, like many other commercial websites, the Mojo website may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. It functions as an identification card and helps identify returning users. A cookie cannot read information off of your hard drive. You can set your browser to alert you of cookies and you can accept or reject them at that time. Mojo may request personal information from you, and from time to time, we may receive personal information from business partners and vendors. At the time we request it, you have the option to not give it to us, but we may not be able to process your request without it.

## How We Use Collected Information

We use non-personal information gathered from users of our website for several purposes, for example, monitoring website performance, improving the user experience and marketing. We use your personal information for several purposes in connection with our business, for example, providing products or services, answering your questions, personalizing your experience on our website, and keeping you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers or other information from us or from our business partners. We may also use your information to send you, or to have our business partners send you, direct marketing information or contact you for market research. If you or your company enters into a business relationship or contract with us, we may collect other types of information from you and use that information for reasons other than described in this Privacy Policy. For example, your personal information may be retained or used by Mojo to verify compliance with the agreement, log software licenses granted, to track software downloaded from those pages, or track usage of other services or applications available on our website or portals.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Because Mojo Networks is a global company and we have customers around the world, your personal information may be shared with other Mojo offices, Mojo affiliates, or agents and service providers around the world. All Mojo companies are governed by this Privacy Policy. Mojo may send your personal information to other companies or people under a variety of circumstances in connection with our business, for example:

  * when we have your consent
  * in order to provide the product or service you have requested
  * to companies who work on behalf of Mojo to provide a product or service to you (we will only provide those companies the information they need to fulfill the need, and in general, we ask that they use it only for such purpose)
  * in an aggregate anonymous manner and in a personal manner for Mojo marketing
  * if we have a good faith belief we are required or permitted to do so under the law, to respond to claims or in connection with a transfer of our business
  * to protect our rights, property or the safety of others, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud

If we are going to send your personal information to other companies or people in connection with their direct marketing, we will ask you for your permission to do so.

## Opting Out

We assume you have given us your consent to collect and use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy unless you take affirmative action to indicate that you do not consent. In general, we will give you an option to opt-out of receiving direct marketing or market research at the time we send it to you. If you wish to withdraw your consent, you should email us at [privacy@mojonetworks.com](mailto:privacy@mojonetworks.com) and specify your request.

## Security

Inside Mojo Networks, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access. When your data is stored outside of Mojo on Mojo’s behalf, we expect our service providers to use reasonable and appropriate steps to protect your data. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where Mojo, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

## Third Party Sites

Our website may contain links to websites operated by other companies. Some of these third-party sites may be co-branded with an Mojo logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by Mojo. Although we choose our business partners carefully, Mojo is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site. Once you have left our website, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party website to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.

## Advertising

As you browse Mojonetworks.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Mojonetworks.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit AdRoll.com to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

## Applicable Law

Our information collection and use practices are subject to the laws of the United States. The laws in the United States may not provide the degree of protection for personal information that is available in other countries. By providing us with your personal information, you acknowledge that your have read this Privacy Policy, understand it, agree to its terms and consent to the transfer and storage of such information outside your resident jurisdiction. If you do not consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website. If you have already provided us with personal information, please send us a written request to [privacy@mojonetworks.com](mailto:privacy@mojonetworks.com) and let us know how you would like us to handle such information.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Mojo Networks will amend this policy from time to time. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for the latest version.

## Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, or wish to correct or change your information, please email us at [privacy@mojonetworks.com](mailto:privacy@mojonetworks.com).
